A Guide to the Records of the Governor's Office, First Lady Anne Holton and Executive Mansion, 2002-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Governor's Office, First Lady Anne Holton and Executive Mansion, 2002-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)
The Library of Virginia
44687
5.43 cu. ft. (16 boxes)
Virginia. Governor's Office. Executive Mansion.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Laura Fields, Office of the Governor, Patrick Henry Building, 1111 E. Broad Street, Richmond, Virginia, accession 42419, transferred and accessioned on 14 January 2010.
Biographical/Historical Information
Anne Holton, Governor Tim Kaine's wife, has devoted her career to serving as an advocate for Virginia's families and children. Holton graduated from Princeton University's Woodrow Wilson School of Public and International Affairs in 1980. She went on to earn her J.D. from Harvard Law School, where she met Tim Kaine and graduated in 1983.
After marrying Tim Kaine, and convincing him to become a Virginian, Anne Holton served for many years as a legal aid lawyer representing low-income families and then as a juvenile and domestic relations district court judge in the City of Richmond. Through her work on the bench, Ms. Holton came to be deeply involved in foster care and adoption, and has worked tirelessly to improve outcomes for Virginia's neglected and abused children. For that work and her service on the bench and in the legal profession, Ms. Holton has received many awards and honors including the YWCA of Richmond 2006 Outstanding Woman Award in the category of law.
As First Lady, Ms. Holton remained dedicated to improving the welfare of Virginia's children and families - and to see that all Virginia children have the opportunity to reach their God-given potential. In January of 2007 she launched her signature initiative, For Keeps: Families for all Virginia Teens. Through the initiative she focused on helping Virginia find and strengthen permanent families particularly for older children in foster care or at risk of entering foster care. For this work, she has received many awards and honors including The Annie E. Casey Foundation Families for Life Award of Distinction in May of 2008.
Holton's move into the Executive Mansion was a homecoming. Her father, Linwood Holton, served as Virginia's governor while Anne was a teenager' from 1970-1974. She and Governor Kaine have 3 children, Nat, Woody and Annella and a family dog, Gina, all of whom enjoyed their tenure in the Mansion.
-Source: Web site of First Lady Anne Holton
Virginia's Executive Mansion has been home, office and center of official entertaining for governors and their families since 1813. It was the second governor's residence constructed in the nation, and is today the oldest governor's residence still used for its original purpose.
The Executive Mansion was Virginia's third state-owned governor's residence. The first two governors under the Constitution of 1776, Patrick Henry and Thomas Jefferson, occupied the colonial Governor's Palace in Williamsburg. In the spring of 1780, Governor Jefferson moved with the government to the new capital in Richmond. For a short period after that relocation, Virginia's governors occupied rental properties.
During the latter part of the 18th century, a second governor's residence was built in Richmond, on almost the same spot the Mansion stands today. The building, a modest frame structure, stood for twelve gubernatorial administrations and was home to three future United States presidents - James Monroe as governor, and John Tyler, Jr. and William Henry Harrison while their fathers were governors.
n 1811, Governor John Tyler, Sr., arguing before the Legislature that the house was "intolerable for a private family," brought about the decision to build the current residence. Under James Monroe's direction and as his last act as Governor, the General Assembly directed "the building of a house for the use of the governor of the commonwealth, on the lot on which the present governor's house stands."
Almost two-hundred years later, with gratitude to Tyler and Monroe, the Mansion remains in the middle of the City. During its long history, the Executive Mansion has been home to 54 Governors and continues to serve not only as a residence to the Chief Executive of Virginia, but also as a place for official state business. There have been 2 major interior renovations (Swanson and Gilmore Administration) and one exterior renovation (Baliles administration) over the long history of the Mansion. The Mansion has seen many famous people and VIPs walk through the mansion, the first floor was almost destroyed by fire, numerous stories of the ghost have been shared over the years, and even hosted three funeral viewings. Families, the children, and their pets have come and gone, but the history that lives within the walls of the Mansion is rich and all who walk through the doors contribute to the legacy of the oldest continually occupied Governor's residence in the United States.
-Taken from Virginia's Executive Mansion Web Site
Scope and Content
The Governor's Office, First Lady Anne Holton and Executive Mansion records are housed in 16 boxes. This collection documents the public activities of First Lady Anne Holton and events held at the Executive Mansion from 2006 to 2010. A few of the Mansion Director's Files contain records of Mansion events during the administration of Governor Mark Warner (2002-2006).
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. First Lady's Files
Series II. Mansion Director's Files
Series III. Mansion Events
Related Material
Web site of First Lady Anne Holton, 2006-2010 part of the Governor Timothy Kaine Administration Collection, 2006-2010.
Web site of First Lady Lisa Collis, 2005-2006 part of the Virginia's Political Landscape, Fall 2005, Web collection.
A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine, Press Office Records, 2004-2010 (bulk 2006-2009).
A Guide to the Governor Mark R. Warner, Press Office Records, 2001-2006 (bulk 2002-2006).
Contents List
- Series I. First Lady's Files, 2006-2009., Extent: 2.98 cu.ft. (boxes 1-9).
  This series is divided into two subseries: Public Event Files and Correspondence. This series documents Anne Holton's official appearances as First Lady during the term of Virginia Governor Tim Kaine (2006-2010). This series also includes the First Lady's correspondence.
  - Subseries I.A. Public Event Files, 2006-2009., Extent: 1.93 cu. ft. (6 boxes)
    This Public Events files are arranged chronologically by the date of the event. These records include event invitations, event briefing forms, event itinerary, event material, correspondence, press releases, and prepared remarks/talking points for Anne Holton. Asha Holloman, Director, Office of the First Lady, scheduled and prepared background materials for these events.
    - Art Works for Virginia Conference, 2006 January 25. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Four Legged Salute from Ringling Bros. and Barnum and Bailey Circus, Richmond, 2006 February 13. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - YWCA Outstanding Women Award Press Conference, Richmond, 2006 February 21. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Read Across America, 2006 March 2. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Women in History, Library of Virginia, 2006 March 2. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Virginia State Police Graduation, Richmond, 2006 March 17. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Math and Science Coalition Awards Ceremony, Richmond, 2006 March 30. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Accept Gift from Ancient Order of Hibernians, Executive Mansion, 2006 March 17. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Monument Avenue 10K, Richmond, 2006 April 1. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - CASA Children's Garden Dedication, Roanoke, 2006 April 5. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - National Folk Festival Press Conference, Executive Mansion, 2006 April 17. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Goochland CASA Volunteer Recognition Dinner, 2006 April 18. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - YWCA Outstanding Women Luncheon, Richmond, 2006 April 21. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Juvenile Detention Alternative Initiative (JDAI) Conference, Glen Allen, 2006 April 27. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Arbor Day Event, Executive Mansion, 2006 April 28. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Magnificent Moms Contest (declined) 2006 May. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Foster Care Month Press Conference, Richmond, 2006 May 4. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Northern Neck CASA Visit, 2006 May 9. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Race for the Cure, Richmond, 2006 May 13. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Beach National Tourism Week and Reception, 2006 May 17. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Commonwealth Challenge Visit, Virginia Beach, 2006 May 17. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Healthy Families Alexandria Metrostage Program Event Fund Raiser, 2006 May 22. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 11th Annual Celebration of Women and Minorities in the Profession Bench Bar Dinner, Richmond, 2006 May 24. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Project STRIVE Graduation, YWCA Richmond, 2006 June 9. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Special Olympics Law Enforcement Torch Run, Richmond, 2006 June 9. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - James River High School Commencement, Richmond, 2006 June 15. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Early Childhood Summit, Exploring Best Practices, Richmond, 2006 July 13. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 9th Annual Virginia Political History Project: Virginia Women and Politics Conference, Richmond, 2006 July 21. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Early Childhood Summit, MCV, Richmond, 2006 August 14. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Get Carried Away with Books and Bugs, Library of Virginia, Richmond, 2006 August 14. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - YMCA Bright Beginnings Event, Richmond, 2006 August 22. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Amy Frederick, Planning for Spouses Build Fundraiser, Richmond, 2006 September 7. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Cool Springs Elementary School Visit, Mechanicsville, 2006 September 12. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Southwest Virginia Tour, 2006 September 18-19. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Richmond CASA Event, 2006 September 15. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia Campaign Kickoff, Richmond, 2006 September 21. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Association of Local Human Services Officials, Virginia Beach, 2006 September 25. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Women's Forum Awareness Month, Richmond, 2006 September 26. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Central Virginia Partnership on Youth Training Day, Richmond, 2006 October 2. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Cooking with Virginia's First Lady, Gloucester, 2006 October 4. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - SPCA Fur Ball, Richmond, 2006 October 6. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - `Radford University Inauguration/Symposium, 2006 October 12. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - School Visit/National Folk Festival, Richmond, 2006 October 13. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - National Folk Festival Events, Richmond, 2006 October 13-15. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Historic Triangle Business and Professional Women Meeting, Williamsburg, 2006 October 17. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - GO READ Program, Fox Elementary School, Richmond, 2006 October 24. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Conference on Parenting, Richmond, 2006 October 26. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Adoption Month Kickoff Luncheon, Richmond, 2006 November 1. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Virginia League of Social Services Executives (VLSSE) Fall Conference, Richmond, 2006 November 1. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Arlington Community Foundation Luncheon, 2006 November 9. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Adoption Celebration Dinner, Danville, 2006 November 10. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Richmond Times-Dispatch Kid's 1 Mile Run, 2006 November 11. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - R.E.B. Awards for Teaching Excellence, Richmond, 2006 November 13. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - National Adoption Day, Richmond, 2006 November 18. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Capital Trail - Greensprings Ribbon Cutting, 2006 November 21. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Virginia First Family/Women Build for South Hampton Roads Habitat for Humanity, Norfolk, 2006 December 1. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Emerging Leaders Class, Patrick Henry High School, Hanover County, 2006 December 5. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Read for 2007: Read for Life Day, Executive Mansion, 2006 December 8. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Metro Richmond Women's Bar Association Luncheon, Richmond, 2007 January 10. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - The Bar Association Lunch Meeting, Richmond, 2007 January 18. (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Henrico CASA Fundraiser, 2007 January 19. (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - CHIP of Greater Richmond Chocoholic, 2007 February 8. (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - First Annual State of Schools Address, Richmond, 2007 February 22. (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - 50th Anniversary of Dr. Seuss' The Cat in the Hat, Arlington, 2007 March 2. (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Linwood Holton Elementary 5K Race and Family Fun Festival, Richmond, 2007 March 10. (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Sorenson Institute Fundraiser Honoring Governor Linwood Holton, Richmond, 2007 March 21. (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - SCAN's Allies in Prevention Awards and Luncheon, Arlington, 2007 March 29. (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Foster Children Celebration, Northumberland Department of Social Services, 2007 May 31. (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Richmond Center Stage Groundbreaking, 2007 June 1. (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Continental Societies Meeting, Virginia Union University, Richmond, 2007 June 2. (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Virginia Legal Aid Society, Lynchburg, 2007 June 7. (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Habitat Build, Richmond, 2007 June 9. (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Richmond Community High School Commencement, 2007 June 14. (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Virginia Legal Aid Award Luncheon, Virginia Beach, 2007 June 15. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - National Association of Counties, Aging Out of Foster Care, Richmond, 2007 July 15. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - National Family Law Symposium, Richmond, 2007 September 16-18. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Systems of Care Conference, Roanoke, 2007 September 16. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - First Annual Mental Health Award's Banquet, Richmond, 2007 September 27. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - National Folk Festival Opening, Richmond, 2007 October 12. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Reflections on Oliver Hill, Sr., Virginia Historical Society, Richmond, 2007 October 28. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Family Lifeline Anniversary, Richmond, 2007 November 1. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - National Adoption Month, Fairfax County, 2007 November 2. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Margaret Vanderhye Event, Falls Church, 2007 November 2. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - OCOC Conference, Richmond, 2007 November 2. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Virginia League of Social Services Executives (VLSSE), Harrisonburg, 2007 November 7. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - VACO Conference, Hot Springs, 2007 November 12-13. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - NHS Induction Ceremony, Maggie Walker Governor's School, Richmond, 2007 November 13. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - WFLO AM/FM Radio Interview, Farmville, 2007 November 14. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - VCCS Meeting, Radford, 2007 November 16. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - National Adoption Day, Fredericksburg, 2007 November 17. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - National Adoption Day, Charlottesville, 2007 November 17. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Christmas Tree Presentation, Executive Mansion, 2007 November 19. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Tax Tribute Ceremony, Executive Mansion, 2007 November 21. (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Habitat for Humanity, National Harbor Event, Washington, D.C., 2007 November 28. (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Tree Lighting Ceremony, State Capitol, 2007 November 30. (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Virginia Association of CSB Directors, 2007 December 4. (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Visual Arts Center Ribbon-Cutting Event, Richmond, 2007 December 7. (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Child Welfare Education and Support Program Seminar, 2007 December 12. (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Testimony Education, General Assembly Building, 2007 December 18. (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Virginia League of Social Services Executives, Richmond, 2007 January 5. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - First Lady's Visit to The Georgetown School, Mechanicsville, 2008 January 15. (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Poverty Law Center Training, University of Richmond, 2008 January 7. (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - FACES Legislative Day, Richmond, 2008 January 20. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - VACSB Legislative Conference, Richmond, 2008 January 22. (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Jepson Center Lecture Series, University of Richmond, 2008 January 24. (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - WRVA Richmond Radio Interview, 2008 January 24. (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Skating Championship, Richmond, 2008 January 25. (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - SPEAK to Humanities Class, Monacan High School, Chesterfield, 2008 January 25. (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - VAPDC Anniversary Event, Richmond, 2008 January 28. (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Job Shadowing Day, 2008 February 5. (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - VALHSO Legislative Meeting, Richmond, 2008 February 6. (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Children's Home Society, Children's Museum of Richmond, 2008 February 9. (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Children's Home Society of Virginia Hollywood Ball, Children's Museum of Richmond, 2008 February 9. (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Virginia Capital Correspondents Association Dinner, Richmond, 2008 February 13. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Child Welfare League of America Annual National Conference, Washington, D.C., 2008 February 26. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Dr. Seuss Celebration, DuPont Elementary School, Hopewell, 2008 March 3. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - National Reading Month, Childrens' Museum, Richmond, 2008 March 6. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Holton 5K, Holton Elementary School, Richmond, 2008 March 8. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - JOHN ADAMS Premiere, Byrd Theater, Richmond, 2008 March 9. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, Poplar Springs Hospital, Petersburg, 2008 March 13. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Historical Marker Dedication, Friends Family Center, Richmond, 2008 March 15. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - APHSA Spring Conference, Washington, D.C., 2008 March 17. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Women's History Month, Freddie Mac, McLean, 2008 March 17. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Child Abuse Prevention Event, Richmond, 2008 April 1. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - New Roof Reception, Historic Smithfield Plantation, Blacksburg, 2008 April 7. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Tech Faculty Women's Club Luncheon, Blacksburg, 2008 April 7. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - YMCA Women of Distinction Luncheon, Norfolk, 2008 April 9. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Speaker, Civil Rights Era, St. Mary's School, Richmond, 2008 April 17. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Virginia High School Leadership Conference, Charlottesville, 2008 April 18. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Children, Youth and Family Services 2008 Community Breakfast, Charlottesville, 2008 April 22. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - New State Fair Groundbreaking, The Meadow, Caroline County, 2008 April 22. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Conference on Disproportionate Minority Contact (DMC) in the Criminal Justice System, Virginia State University, 2008 April 24. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Foster Care Month Dinner, Richmond, 2008 May 1. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Virginia's Rule of Law Conference, Richmond, 2008 May 1. (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Junior League Book and Author Dinner, Richmond, 2008 May 6. (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - CVLAS and Charlottesville Legal Aid Justice Center, Richmond, 2008 May 13. (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Foster Care Month Dinner, Lutheran Family Services, Portsmouth, 2008 May 15. (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - VCU School of Social Work Graduation, Richmond, 2008 May 16. (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Women's Day Program, St. Elizabeth's Church, Richmond, 2008 May 18. (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Big Read in Virginia Celebration, Library of Virginia, Richmond, 2008 May 29. (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Beat The Odds Awards, Gainesville, 2008 May 30. (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Work/Life Balance Conference, Richmond, 2008 May 30. (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Foster Care/CSA Bill Signing, Family Service of Roanoke Valley, 2008 May 30. (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Ride for Kids, Glen Allen, 2008 June 1. (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - TowneBank Williamsburg Executive Women's Network, 2008 June 4. (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Special Olympics Torch Run Ceremony, State Capitol, 2008 June 6. (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Open High School Graduation, Richmond, 2008 June 10. (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - 5th Grade Moving Up Ceremony, Longdale Elementary School, Glen Allen, 2008 June 11. (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Ribbon Cutting, Virginia Interfaith Center, Richmond, 2008 June 23. (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Youth Leadership Forum Day, State Capitol, 2008 July 17. (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Homeward Conference, Capital One, Goochland County, 2008 September 11. (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Adult Forum Class, Second Presbyterian Church, Richmond, 2008 September 14. (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - First Annual Great Expectations Education Forum, Richmond, 2008 September 13. (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Step Up for Kids Rally, Bell Tower, Richmond, 2008. (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Virginia Press Women's Newsmaker of the Year, Richmond Times-Dispatch, 2008 September 26. (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - SupportOne 10th Anniversary, Richmond, 2008 October 1. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Petersburg Chamber Luncheon, 2008 October 2. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Richmond Folk Festival, Ukrop's/First Market Stage, 2008 October 10. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 11th Annual Literary Awards, Library of Virginia, Richmond, 2008 October 18. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - CASA State Conference, Williamsburg, 2008 November 7. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Press Conference, Henrico Doctor's Hospital, 2008 November 12. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Legal Aid Benefit, Richmond, 2008 November 13. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Voices for Change Awards, Executive Mansion, 2008 November 16. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Harrisonburg/Rockingham County Community Summit on Strengthening Children and Families, James Madison University, 2008 November 18. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - First Lady's Forum, James Madison University, 2008 November 18. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Excellence Awards, Richmond, 2008 December 4. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Hadassah Ceremony, Executive Mansion, 2008 December 11. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Family Law Clinic Dedication, Richmond, 2009 March 3. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Project HOPE Conference, Williamsburg, 2009 March 3. (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Dr. Seuss Week, Glen Allen Elementary, 2009 March 5. (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Mystery Reader, Longan Elementary School, Richmond, 2009 March 12. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Book Presentation, Library of Virginia, Richmond, 2009 March 12. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Leadership Class, Radford University, 2009 March 17. (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Transformation Forum, Radford University, 2009 March 17. (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Reading to Children, Weinstein JCC, Richmond, 2009 March 20. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Prevent Child Abuse Kick-Off, Richmond, 2009 April 1. (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - No Child Left Inside, Richmond, 2009 April 28. (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Project HOPE Conference, Williasmburg, 2009 April 28. (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Law Day Program, Lakeside Elementary School, Richmond, 2009 May 1. (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Girl Scout Leadership Awards, Richmond, 2009 May 5. (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - University of Mary Washington Graduation, Fredericksburg, 2009 May 9. (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Council of Churches, Richmond, 2009 May 18. (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Women in Government, Dominion VA Power, Richmond, 2009 May 18. (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - VDSS Employee Recognition Event, 2009 May 19. (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Charlottesville Bar Association Meeting, 2009 May 21. (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Foster Parent Recognition, Hampton, 2009 May 26. (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Virginia Poverty Law Center's 30th Anniversary Celebration, Richmond, 2009 May 28. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Dominion Free Clinics Donation, Fan Free Clinic, Richmond, 2009 June 2. (Box 5, Folder 33)